Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan), 1852-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Deans of the Law School, 1852-1999
  - Programs and Projects
    - Legal Assistance for Urban Communities (LAUC)
      Legal Assistance for Urban Communities program served as a legal resource for non-profit organizations in and around Detroit. The staff and students provided services relating to incorporation and taxation, as well as counsel relating to legal cases. The LAUC files--retained in their original order--are arranged by name of client. They contain correspondence, memoranda, research materials, and reports and legal documents produced by students. Clients represented here include Alternatives for Girls, Cass Community Non-Profit Housing Corporation, Lawrence-Loves-Linwood and Dexter Development Organization, and Weatherization and Retrofit Maintenance (WARM) Construction.
      - Alternatives for Girls (AFG)
        - Background Information, 1990-1993 (Box 98)
        - Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box 98)
        - Michigan Housing Trust--Research Park, 1991 (Box 98)
        - Progress Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 98)
        - St. Patrick's Center, 1991 (Box 98)
        - Security Deposit Agreements, 1992 (Box 98)
        - Slater Contract, 1992-1993 (Box 98)
        - United Community for Housing Coalition Contract, 1992-1993 (Box 98)
        - Zoning Issues, 1992 (Box 98)
      - Cass Community Non-Profit Housing Corporation (CCNPHC)
        - Articles of Incorporation, 1991 (Box 98)
        - Bookkeeping System Proposal, 1991 (Box 98)
        - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1991-1993 (Box 98)
        - Marie Apartments, 1991-1992 (Box 98)
        - Progress Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 98)
        - Tax Exempt Status, 1991-1992 (Box 98)
      - Cass Corridor Neighborhood Development Corporation (CCNDC) (Box 99)
        - Background Information, 1990-1991 (Box 99)
        - Correspondence and Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
          (includes two 5 1/4" computer discs)
      - Courts of Calanthe and Knights of Pythias
        - Articles of Incorporation and Merger Information, 1952; 1992-1993 (Box 99)
          (includes microfiche copy of original articles)
        - Background and Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 99)
        - Notes and Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box 99)
        - Tax Exempt Status, 1992-1993 (Box 99)
          (includes one 3 1/2" computer disc)
      - Housing Strategies
        - Drug Forfeiture Law, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - House Bill #4670 (Property tax foreclosure), 1991 (Box 99)
        - Community Meetings and Reports
          - April 1991 (Box 99)
          - November 1991 (Box 99)
          - March 1992 (Box 99)
        - Michigan Receivership Law, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - Neighborhood Enterprise Zone Act, 1992 (Box 99)
        - Housing Tax Credit, 1991 (Box 99)
        - Michigan Housing Development Authority (MSHDA), 1992 (Box 99)
        - Progress Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
      - Jeremiah Project, 1994 (Box 99)
      - Lawrence-Loves-Linwood and Dexter Development Organization
        - Articles of Incorporation, 1992 (Box 99)
        - Background/Resources, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - By-Laws, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 99)
        - Progress Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
      - Lighthouse/Unity Park, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 99)
      - Nortown Community Development Corporation, 1992 (Box 99)
      - Nuisance Abatement Ordinance, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
      - Preserve Low Income Affordable Housing Now (PLAN), 1992-1993 (Box 99)
      - Warren/Conner Development Coalition (WCDC)
        - Background Materials, 1990-1992 (Box 99)
        - Progress Reports, 1991 (Box 99)
        - Real Estate, 1990-1993 (Box 99)
        - Section 1031 and Bargain Sale Memorandum, 1992 (Box 99)
        - Technical Advisors Group, 1990-1991 (Box 99)
      - We Care Non-Profit Housing Corporation, 1993 (Box 99)
      - Weatherization and Retrofit Maintenance (WARM) Construction
        - Documents, 1992/93 (Box 99)
          (3.5" Computer disc)
        - Articles of Incorporation, 1993 (Box 99)
        - Background Information/History, 1987-1992 (Box 99)
        - Board Minutes and Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - Bylaws, 1992 (Box 99)
        - Consultant Agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - Corporate Resolutions, 1992 (Box 99)
        - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 99)
        - Final Documents, June 9, 1992 (Box 99)
        - Loan Agreement, 1991-1992 (Box 99)
        - Membership Agreement, 1993 (Box 99)
        - Notes and Memoranda, 1992-1993 (Box 99)
        - Progress Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 99)
    - Minority Affairs Program (MAP--formerly Minority Academic Advancement Program)
      The Minority Affairs Program was established to aid minority students in the transition to law school. The program employs upper-class student instructors and also uses the services of willing faculty members for workshops and practice exams. It has generally been overseen by an assistant dean at the Law School. The MAP files include correspondence, memoranda, student lists, reports, syllabi, and student evaluations of the program for terms between 1986 and 1995.
      - 1982-1995, 26 folders (Box 100)
        - Correspondence, memos, student lists, reports, syllabi, etc. (Box 100)
      - 1996, 2 folders (Box 101)
      - Evaluations, 1986-1995
        - Faculty Advancement, 1986-1988 (Box 101)
        - Summer 1987 (Box 101)
        - Fall 1987 (Box 101)
        - Fall 1989 (Box 101)
        - Winter 1990 (Box 101)
        - Fall 1990 (Box 101)
        - Summer 1991 (Box 101)
        - Fall 1991 (Box 101)
        - Fall 1992 (Box 101)
        - Summer 1992 (Box 101)
        - Summer 1993 (Box 101)
        - Fall 1995 (Box 101)
      - Instructor Applications for, 1996-1997; 1996 (Box 119)
        [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2026 ]
      - Multicultural Efforts, 1997 (Box 101)
      - Study Aids, 1991-1993 (Box 101)
      - Summer Program Donations, 1992 (Box 101)
  - Topical Files
    The Topical Files series includes two sub-series. These two topical files overlap with those in other Law School accessions; the researcher is advised to inspect each accession.
    - Topical Files [E. Blythe Stason], 1927-1961
      The subseries, Topical File, 1927-1961, was added to the Law School record group from the personal papers of E. Blythe Stason, Dean of the Law School from 1939 through 1960.
      - Administrative Committee, 1956-1961 (Box 101)
      - American Bar Association survey of the legal profession, 1949 (Box 101)
      - American Journal of Comparative Law, 1951 (Box 101)
      - American Judicature Society, 1927-1940; 4 folders (Box 101)
      - California Bar examinations, 1932-1952 (Box 101)
      - Case Club, 1954-1959 (Box 101)
      - DeWitt (Clyde) trust and related, 1939-1957; 5 folders (Box 101)
      - Editorial Board (Box 102)
      - Editorial Committee (Box 102)
      - English attorneys (correspondence with), 1949 (Box 102)
      - Goddard (Edwin) estate, 1944-1950 (Box 102)
      - Graduate and Research Committee, 1935-1961; 6 folders (Box 102)
      - Institute of Public Administration Executive Committee, 1945-1951 (Box 102)
      - Inter-American Bar Association forums, etc., 1947-1949; 2 folders (Box 102)
      - International Law Forum, 1948; 2 folders (Box 102)
      - James B. Angell Foundation, 1945 (Box 102)
      - Law Institute/Roundtables, 1939-1942; 4 folders (Box 102)
      - Law School Admission Policy, 1946/47-1954 (scattered) (Box 102)
      - Law School Alumni statistics and other data, 1950 (Box 102)
      - Law School Centennial, 1959-1960 (Box 102)
      - Law School histories (Box 103)
      - Law School-various reports, 1934-1941 (Box 103)
      - Law School-various reports, 1940-1961 (Box 103)
      - Law School miscellaneous, 1955-1960 (Box 103)
      - Law School planning memoranda, etc (Box 103)
      - Legal Aptitude Test, Committee on (Box 103)
      - Legislative Research Center, 1950-1959 (Box 103)
      - Michigan Law Review (Box 103)
      - Michigan State (validity of name change) (Box 103)
      - Personnel Committee, 1957 (Box 103)
      - Planning Committee, 1957-1959; 2 folders (Box 103)
      - Post-World War II (Box 103)
      - Planning for the Law School (Box 103)
      - Planning for the University (Box 103)
      - Refresher courses for veterans (Box 103)
      - Rule of Law Seminar, 1956-1957 (Box 103)
      - Scholarship Committee, 1940-1961 (Box 103)
      - Stason faculty gift and portrait presentations, 1960 (Box 103)
      - State Bar of Michigan (Box 103)
      - Student Bar Association, 1956-1959 (Box 103)
      - Summer Session, Executive Committee, 1945-1950 (Box 103)
    - Topical Files, 1954-1997
      The subseries, Topical Files, 1954-1997, covers the tenure of several deans. Of special interest may be the Placement Office files, where material relating to the 1988 ban on CIA recruitment at the school is located; the Capital Campaign files, which contain correspondence relating to the campaign of the late 1970s to raise funds to build the Law Library Addition; and the Academic Policy Group Subcommittee on Sexual Orientation files, a task force chaired by Dean Bollinger in 1992 and 1993.
      - Academic Policy Group (APG) Subcommittee on Sexual Orientation, 1991-1994 (Box 104)
        (Deans Committee on Lesbian, Gay and Bisexual Concerns)
      - Academic Regulations
        - 1979 (Box 104)
        - MCL/LLM, 1982 (Box 104)
      - Admissions
        - Admissions Office Reports, 1959-1979; 2 folders (Box 104)
        - Bi-residency, 1992 (Box 104)
        - Deans Scholars, 1990 (Box 104)
        - General, 1971-1990; 2 folders (Box 104)
        - Minority, 1972-1984; 2 folders (Box 104)
        - Recruiting, 1966-1967 (Box 104)
      - Affirmative Action, 1975-1985 (Box 104)
      - Alumni Reunion and Law Forum, 1980-1986 (Box 104)
      - Alumni Survey
        - Classes of 1951-1956, 1966-[1971] (Box 104)
        - Classes of, 1969-1979; 1978-1985 (Box 104)
      - American Association of Law Schools
        - 1987-1993 (Box 104)
        - AALS Constitutional Law Conference, 1993 (Box 104)
      - American Bar Association
        - 1971-1994 (Box 104)
        - Reinspections
          - 1969-1970 (Box 104)
          - 1977-1980 (Box 104)
          - 1985-1986 (Box 105)
        - Standard 212 (Affirmative Action Requirements), 1979-1980 (Box 105)
      - American Bar Foundation, 1971-1985 (Box 105)
      - Appellate Defender Program (David Chambers), 1971-1973 (Box 105)
      - Audit by State of Michigan Audit General, 1978 (Box 105)
      - Bakke Case (Education Quotas), 1977-1978 (Box 105)
      - Bar Exam Results
        - Michigan, 1977-1989 (Box 119)
          [SR RESTRICTED until 2064 ]
        - Minorities, 1981 (Box 119)
          [SR RESTRICTED until 2056 ]
        - Minorities (compiled), 1977-1980 (Box 105)
        - Other States, 1982-1994 (Box 119)
          [SR RESTRICTED until 2069 ]
      - Black Student Scholarship Fund, 1968; undated (Box 105)
      - Broomfield Essay Contest, 1970-1979 (Box 105)
      - Brussels-Michigan Cooperation, 1971-1985 (Box 105)
      - Budgeting, 1978-1994; 32 folders (Box 105)
      - Capital Campaign
        - 1972-1981, 8 folders (Box 106)
        - Getty, J. Paul, 1975-1976 (Box 106)
        - Humphrey, George M. II, 1973-1979 (Box 106)
        - Jones, Robert A. (Development Director), 1973-1979; 3 folders (Box 106)
        - Kresge Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 106)
        - Library Addition, 1978-1984 (Box 106)
        - Library Dedication, October 30-31, 1981
          - Correspondence and Memoranda, 1980-1982 (Box 106)
          - Invitations (includes lists of donors), 1980-1981 (Box 106)
          - Speeches, 1981 (Box 106)
        - Lilly Endowment, 1973-1974 (Box 106)
        - Long, Thomas G., 1973-1977 (Box 106)
        - Souther, Calvin N., 1974-1980 (Box 106)
        - Towsley, Harry A., 1974-1979 (Box 106)
      - Christmas Party, 1975-1979; undated (Box 106)
      - Class Scheduling (includes list of new and visiting faculty), 1972-1986 (Box 106)
      - Clinical Law
        - 1970-1991, 2 folders (Box 107)
        - All Programs, 1976-1993 (Box 107)
        - Clinical Appointments, 1987-1993 (Box 107)
        - Clinical Law II
          - Pepe, Steven, 1975-1978 (Box 107)
          - Tax Program, 1976-1979 (Box 107)
          - Committee on Status of Clinicians, 1987 (Box 107)
        - Ethics and Psychiatry, 1974-1977 (Box 107)
        - Clinical Law Proposal to Center for Research on Learning and Teaching, 1976 (Box 107)
      - Compliance Reports (Minority Group Data--Employees), 1965-1970 (Box 107)
      - Computing Center, 1967; 1982-1987 (Box 107)
      - Curriculum, 1972-1984 (Box 107)
      - Darrow, Clarence Scholarship, 1995-1996 (Box 107)
      - DeWitt, Clyde Estate, 1956-1962 (Box 107)
      - Diploma Privilege, 1979 (Box 107)
      - Disciplinary Statutes and Regulations, 1968-1981 (Box 107)
      - Endowment Fund Reports, 1983-1990 (Box 107)
      - Establishment of a New Law School in Michigan, 1967 (Box 107)
      - Ethics, undated (Box 107)
      - Evaluation and Planning--Phase I, 1976 (Box 107)
      - Fellowships
        - Tony Patio, 1984-1985 (Box 107)
      - Financial Aid, 1971-1986; 2 folders (Box 107)
      - Ford Foundation
        - Annual Reports (See also Box 54), 1969-1974 (Box 107)
        - Desegregation Study (Paul Dimond), 1978-1981 (Box 107)
        - Miscellaneous, 1954-1972; 3 folders (Box 107)
      - Foreign Students, 1971-1981 (Box 108)
      - Foundations (House Resolution #13270), 1969 (Box 108)
      - Gifts
        - Shapero, Harold M., 1982 (Box 108)
        - Sullivan, Robert A. Professorship, 1978-1991 (Box 108)
        - Willey, Roy E., 1978-1997 (Box 108)
      - Grade Guidelines, 1979 (Box 108)
      - Great Lakes Natural Resource Clinic, 1980-1985; 2 folders (Box 108)
      - History
        - Class of 1878, 1977 (Box 108)
        - Hargo, Gabriel F. (First Black Person to Graduate from University of Michigan Law School, 1870), 1993-1994 (Box 108)
        - Histories by Henry Wade Rogers, 1969; 1989 (Box 108)
        - "The Law School, 1940-1973," by Charles A. Lowenhaupt (Box 108)
      - Humphrey, George M., 1965-1976 (Box 108)
      - Immigration Law Project, 1986 (Box 108)
      - Information, Technology and Law--Research Proposal, 1970 (Box 108)
      - International and Comparative Law, 1971-1977 (Box 108)
      - Japanese Law Programs, 1978-1989 (Box 108)
      - Joint Programs
        - Law and Economics, 1975-1983 (Box 108)
        - Miscellaneous, 1980-1985 (Box 108)
      - Journal of Law Reform, 1968-1994 (Box 108)
      - Judiciary Council, 1967-1977 (Box 108)
      - King, Martin Luther Jr. Day, 1991-1995; 4 folders (Box 108)
      - Knappen Club, 1981 (Box 108)
      - Law Clerks, 1979-1994 (Box 108)
      - Law Firm's Fund Letters, 1967 (Box 108)
      - Law Library, 1971-1988 (Box 108)
      - Law Library Addition Law Suit, 1984 (Box 108)
      - Law Quadrangle Notes, 1982-1992 (Box 108)
      - Law Review, 1971-1994; 2 folders (Box 108)
      - Law School, 1971-1986 (Box 109)
      - Law School Fund
        - 1961-1992, 6 folders (Box 109)
        - Metzger Account, 1972-1991 (Box 109)
        - Napoleon, Greg, 1986-1987 (Box 109)
        - National Committee Annual Meeting, 1979 (Box 109)
      - Law School Rankings, 1977-1994 (Box 109)
      - Lawyers Club
        - 1971-1994, 2 folders (Box 109)
        - Agreement with University Housing and Bylaws, 1968-1978 (Box 109)
        - Annual Meeting of the Board of Governors, 1971-1979; 9 folders (Box 109)
        - Budgeting, 1969-1978 (Box 109)
        - Correspondence, 1968-1977 (Box 109)
        - Food Service Analysis, 1969-1978 (Box 109)
        - History
          - Contract Negotiation by Robert G. Kuhbach, 1972 (Box 109)
        - Operational Survey, 1969-1970 (Box 109)
        - Student Board of Directors, 1968-1969 (Box 110)
        - Tapestries, 1970-1976 (Box 110)
        - Terms of Members of Board of Governors, 1961-1971 (Box 110)
      - Manuscript Format Rules, 1964; undated (Box 110)
      - Michigan Constitution (Judicial Article review), 1971 (Box 110)
      - Michigan Journalism Fellows Program (Charles Eisendrath), 1990-1993 (Box 110)
      - Michigan Journal of International Law (formerly Michigan Yearbook of International Legal Studies), 1978-1994; 2 folders (Box 110)
      - Michigan State Bar, 1965-1985 (Box 110)
      - Michigan State Board of Law Examiners, 1958-1964 (Box 110)
      - Minorities
        - 1972-1983 (Box 110)
        - Advisors, 1975-1980 (Box 110)
        - Inquiries, 1968-1969 (Box 110)
        - Students, 1975-1977 (Box 110)
      - Nathan Burkan Memorial Competition (ASCAP), 1967-1987 (Box 110)
      - Nederlander, Robert E., 1975-1979 (Box 110)
      - News Clippings--Dean Allen and Law School, 1966 (Box 110)
      - Orientation, 1979-1986 (Box 110)
      - Personnel
        - Complaints, 1971-1974 (Box 110)
      - Placement Office
        - 1962-1991, 5 folders (Box 110)
        - CIA
          - 1988 (Box 110)
          - Demonstration, 1988 (Box 110)
        - Class Survey (1952), 1968 (Box 110)
        - FBI, 1988-1990 (Box 110)
        - Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 110)
        - Placement and Sexual Orientation, 1988 (Box 110)
      - Plaques in the Law School, 1969 (Box 110)
      - Problems and Research Program, 1968 (Box 110)
      - Recordkeeping in the Law School, 1968 (Box 110)
      - Reunions
        - European Alumni Reunion, 1989
          - Transcripts and Tapes of Addresses
            - Lee C. Bollinger (Box 111)
              (includes 5 1/4" computer disc)
            - Virginia Gordon (Box 111)
            - Eric Stein (Box 111)
        - International Alumni Reunion, 1991 (Box 111)
      - Scalia Report, 1986 (Box 111)
      - Scholarships and Fellowships
        - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1970-1971 (Box 111)
      - Selective Service Letters Written for Law Students, 1968-1969 (Box 111)
      - Selective Service System Statement, 1968 (Box 111)
      - Self Study of Law School, 1978; 1985; 2 folders (Box 111)
      - Seminar (Research), 1985-1986 (Box 111)
      - Seminar on University Priorities (SOUP), 1980-1983 (Box 111)
      - Senior Day
        - 1968-1994, 10 folders (Box 111)
        - Speakers, 1966-1988 (Box 111)
      - Sesquicentennial, 1965-1966 (Box 111)
      - Sexual Orientation (Box 111)
        (see APG Subcommittee on Sexual Orientation)
      - State Capital Outlay Request, 1966 (Box 111)
      - Student Enrollment, 1972; 1983 (Box 111)
      - Student Lounge, 1982-1984 (Box 111)
      - Students Interested in Teaching, 1982-1992 (Box 111)
      - Summer Legal Aid Program, 1972; undated (Box 111)
      - Sunderland Visiting Fellowships (Dwight F. Benton), 1982-1992 (Box 111)
      - Supreme Court Clerkships, 1964-1965 (Box 111)
      - Survey--Public Service Positions, 1987-1988 (Box 111)
      - University Presidents
        - Fleming, Robben, 1968-1977 (Box 112)
        - Shapiro, Harold, 1980-1987 (Box 112)
      - Vietnam War--Resolution Adopted by the Faculty of the Law School, 1969 (Box 112)
      - Waldenwoods Retreat, 1972 (Box 112)
      - Writing and Advocacy Program, 1973-1985 (Box 112)
      - Writing Programs, 1971 (Box 112)
- Faculty Files, 1859-1960
  The Faculty Files series is comprised of six subseries: Faculty Minutes, 1859-1960; Miscellaneous files; (Pre-1985 accessions) Memos to the Faculty; Personnel Files; Publications, Research and Activities; and Salaries (1999 Accession).
  - Faculty Minutes, 1859-1960
    The Faculty Minutes consists of bound volumes of faculty meeting minutes from 1859 to 1870 and 1894 to 1960. Minutes between 1871 and 1894 are unaccounted for.
    - 1859-March 1870 (Box 59)
    - May 1894-June 1895 (Box 59)
    - September 1895-June 1901 (Box 59)
    - 1901-1910 (Box 60)
    - 1910-1920 (Box 60)
    - 1920-1930 (Box 60)
    - 1930-1940, 2 volumes (Box 60)
    - 1940-1945 (Box 61)
    - 1945-1950, 2 volumes (Box 61)
    - 1950-1955, 2 volumes (Box 61)
    - 1955-1960, 4 volumes (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous Files
    The Miscellaneous Files includes two bound volumes recording lectures given in the Law School between 1870 and 1897. Information on lectures typically includes date, presenter, and title or subject. For copies of many of these lectures, consult the finding aid for University of Michigan Law School. Law Lectures, 1881-1919.
    - Index to Pound's Notes (Ames and Smith, Pound Edition), undated (Box 63)
    - Record of Lectures in the Law School, 1870-1897; 2 volumes (Box 63)
  - Memos to the Faculty
    Memos to the Faculty are generally from the dean, and cover the topics of interest to the faculty as a group between 1966 and 1994.
    - 1966-1994, 6 folders (Box 112)
  - Personnel Files
    There are approximately 5 linear feet of Personnel Files. Personnel files are closed for thirty years from the date of creation. The files usually contain evaluations, curriculum vitae and obituaries for tenured faculty members. In some cases, they also contain grant proposals, syllabi, or correspondence about teaching or professional activities.
    - Evaluations of Adjunct Faculty, 1979; 1982 (Box 119)
    - Aaron, Benjamin (Win 1979--Labor Law), 1978-1979 (Box 119)
    - Abe, Haruo, 1961-1962 (Box 112)
    - Adams, William James, 1977-1981 (Box 119)
    - Adelman, Martin, 1981-1982 (Box 119)
    - Aigler, Ralph W. (Member of the faculty, 1910-1954), 1964-1967 (Box 112)
    - Alexander, Gabriel N., 1956 (Box 112)
    - Alexander, Gregory S. (Sum 1982--Trusts and Estates I) (Box 119)
    - Alexander, Susan (Instructor, 1972/73) (Box 119)
    - Ali, Mohammed Ibrahim Ahmad (Win 1977 and Win 1979), 1976-1977 (Box 119)
    - Allen, Ronald J. (Sum 1982--Criminal Law) (Box 119)
    - Alschuler, Albert W. (Sum 1975) (Box 119)
    - Andersen, Jerry Richard, 1960 (Box 112)
    - Andersen, William R. (Win 1983), 1982 (Box 119)
    - Andrews, William D. (Sum 1975) (Box 119)
    - Archer, Edward P., 1967 (Box 112)
    - Areen, Judith C., 1975-1976 (Box 119)
    - Arnold, Morris S. (Sum 1981--Trusts and Estates I), 1979-1981 (Box 119)
    - Asimow, Michael R. (Sum 1984) (Box 119)
    - Axelrod, Bruce (Win 1977) (Box 119)
    - Babcock, Barbara A. (Sum 1976) (Box 119)
    - Baier, Paul R., 1970 (Box 112)
    - Baldonado, Charles, 1976 (Box 119)
    - Baptista, Luiz Olavo (Win 1979), 1978 (Box 119)
    - Barbour, Willard T. (Member of the faculty, 1912-1919), undated (Box 112)
    - Barker, Vincent L. (Adjunct Lecturer, 1979-1984), 1979-1997 (Box 119)
      [PR RESTRICTED until January 1, 2027 ]
    - Bart, Susan T. (Fall 1996) (Box 119)
    - Barton, John H. (Fall 1981) (Box 119)
    - Bartosic, Florian J. (Sum 1972 and Sum 1974), 1972-1973 (Box 119)
    - Bassett, Scott G. (Clinical Instructor, 1984/85--Child Advocacy Clinic), 1984-1985 (Box 119)
    - Bates, Marion Virginia, 1951 (Box 112)
    - Bator, Paul M. (Sum 1976) (Box 119)
    - Battles, Ronald M., 1970-1972 (Box 119)
    - Bauer, Joseph P. (Instructor, 1972/73) (Box 119)
    - Baxter, Richard R., 1963-1964 (Box 112)
    - Bayne, David C., 1966-1967 (Box 112)
    - Becker, David M., 1962 (Box 112)
    - Benson, Dennis, 1974 (Box 119)
    - Berg, Rolf E. (Adjunct Lecturer, Jan 1, 1981-April 30, 1982) (Box 119)
    - Berman, William H., 1958 (Box 112)
    - Bernini, Giorgio V., 1958 (Box 112)
    - Bernstein, Neil N. (Sum 1972) (Box 119)
    - Betts, Helen L., 1954-1994 (Box 119)
    - Betz, Esther, 1957-1963 (Box 112)
    - Beytagh, Francis X., Jr. (1983/84) (Box 119)
    - Bianchi, Evelyn Victoria, 1953 (Box 112)
    - Bianchi, Rinaldo L. (1955/56 and Win 1977), 1955-1977 (Box 119)
    - Bilder, Richard B. (Sum 1971), 1970-1971 (Box 112)
    - Birmingham, Hobart M., 1973 (Box 119)